AZAR BARFIPOUR

SUMMARY

Former software support specialist for more than 4 years with a background of software engineering turned to front-end developer. Working with the biggest companies in my country and collaborating in many teams alongside having a great experience as a student in Vancouver and learning many updated technologies makes me feel comfortable to join your company and work as a front-end developer.

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING: JavaScript, Ruby, HTML5, CSS3

FRAMEWORKS, LIBRARIES AND ENVIRONMENTS: React.js, jQuery, SASS, Bootstrap

SYSTEMS, CMS AND DATABASES: git, github, firebase, PostgreSQL, SQLserver, Oracle

LANGUAGES: Persian, English TOEFL: R19, L21, S23, W21

Academic English Preparation(UAP): 86.98%

PROJECTS

Feb 2022 Meetup App

A book event application for searching and booking events Technical specifications: react, HTML, css, firebase

Portfolio Website Mar 2022

Technical specifications: HTML, css, BootStrap, JavaScript, JQuery

EDUCATION

Web Development Diploma | CICCC, Vancouver, Canada

Aug 2021 - present

HTML, CSS, React.js, Node.js, SQL, Python etc.

UAP | University Canada West, Vancouver, Canada

Apr 2021

Academic English course

Computer Software Engineering B.S. | UOK, Sanandaj, IRAN

Feb 2015

Thesis: Web site design by Joomla Advisor: Fardin Akhlaghian

EMPLOYMENT

Front End Developer | Volunteer at Freelivenet, Vancouver May 2022 - present

- Testing and developing an Angular CRM
- Working with git and Bitbucket

Data Entry | Volunteer at Terry Beech Office, Vancouver

July 2021

• Analyze people surveys and enter into the Application

Software Support Specialist | Behban software Co, Tehran

Sep 2015 - Oct 2020

- Creating more than 100 reports for many big companies from their data.
- Working with huge databases from one of the biggest oil company in my country
- Debugging and solving more than 100 customers in each day
- Working with multiple teams at company and collaborating with them
- Creating forms in ASP classic by using asp,html,css, JavaScript and Sql
- Travel around the country to install and teach The application To clients
- Enhancing functions and security of applications which increased our clients by 20%
- Testing multiple applications to increase their user interfaces and functionality